Wednesday, June 19, 2024

 Lights?

    * \-----

Menu
----

Knowledgebase
=============

1. [Portal Home](https://www.le-vpn.com/clients/index.php)
2. [Knowledgebase](https://www.le-vpn.com/clients/knowledgebase.php)
3. [Frequently Asked Questions](https://le-vpn.com/clients/knowledgebase/1/Frequently-Asked-Questions)
4. [Terms of use](https://le-vpn.com/clients/knowledgebase/29/Terms-of-use)
5. Terms of use

Terms of use
------------

**Privacy Policy & Terms of Use**

**Introduction**

VTNV Solutions Limited dba LE VPN (hereinafter referred to as “LE VPN”, "we", "us" and "our"), provides you with the website [le-vpn.com](https://www.le-vpn.com/) (hereinafter referred to as our “Site") and the services available through it (hereinafter referred to as the “Le VPN Service”).

The present privacy policy and terms of use explain how we provide our subscribers (“you”) with the Le VPN Service and the ways that you are permitted to make use of the Le VPN Service.

The Le VPN Service provides you with access to our network of servers around the world. We also provide various software tools such as the LE VPN software for desktop computers and laptops, mobile apps for iOS and Android devices (the "Software"), which allow you to connect easily to our Le VPN Service although you may connect without using our Software. The Le VPN Service also includes a SmartDNS service for desktop computers, laptops, mobile devices, routers, smartTVs and game consoles.

Our privacy policy and terms of use (hereinafter referred to as the "Privacy Policy" and the "Terms of Use") apply when you use our Le VPN Service. Please read the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use carefully before you purchase a subscription for, or start to use, our Le VPN Service. By using our Le VPN Service, you indicate that you accept the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use and that you agree to abide by them. If you do not agree to them, please refrain from using our Le VPN Service.

We are a provider of web privacy and security tools and therefore we are deeply committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy (together with any other documents referred to in it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we, as data controller of your personal data that you provide to us, will treat it. 

Our privacy policy applies when you use our Site. Please read the Privacy Policy carefully before you start using our Site. By using our Site, you indicate that you accept the Privacy Policy and that you agree to abide by it. If you do not agree to our Privacy Policy and/or Terms of Use, please refrain from using our Site.

We may revise our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use by posting an updated version to this web page to reflect changes in our privacy practices, market conditions affecting our business, changes in technology or our business model, changes in relevant laws and regulatory requirements, and changes in our systems. We encourage you to periodically check this page to take notice of any changes we make, as they are binding upon you.

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use, you can [contact our technical support team](https://www.le-vpn.com/clients/submitticket.php?language=english).

**I - Privacy Policy**

**1\. Information we collect from you**

What data we collect: When you register we will collect your username, email address, password (encrypted) and IP address. We may also collect your first and last names, company name, postal address and phone number if you decide to disclose such information to us. By using our Site, you confirm that all data provided by you is accurate and not misleading.

Why we need this data: We will need your username and password in order to provide you with access to the web based control panel and to our downloadable Software. We will need your email address in case you forget your password or wish to receive email newsletters. Your IP address is logged by us so that we can prevent any spam, fraud or abuse of our Site and our Le VPN Service. If you do not use any of our Le VPN Service, we may decide to store this data for up to five years after your account has become inactive. If you continue to use our Le VPN Service, we will store your registration data for as long as you are using one of our services or have an active account, and for up to five years after that. We may keep your registration data for an extended period as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

How we use this data: we use this data to provide the Le VPN Service to you and to prevent fraud and abuse. From time to time we may email you news, updates and sales offers which you can easily opt out of receiving by clicking the "unsubscribe" in the relevant email. We use customer contact information to send customers information about our company and its products and services. Indeed, we may send marketing and service usage related communications to the clients, and the clients have an option to opt out of LE VPN marketing communication list via an unsubscribe option.

When you contact us: If you contact us through our Site for any reason (e.g. by email) we will generally store these communications for as long as necessary or required under law.

Payment Information: If you opt to pay for the use of our Le VPN Service, we will use third party payment processors to collect payments from you. Our third party payment processors are properly regulated and authorised to handle your payment information and is prohibited from using your personal information for promotional purposes or for any other purposes other than providing these payment services to us. We never handle or store your payment information, as this is done on our behalf by our third party payment processors. We are not responsible for the manner in which our third party payment processors will handle your transactions and you should refer to such third party payment processors' privacy policy to see how it uses your data.

Le VPN Service: We will store (i) a time stamp and IP address when you connect and disconnect to our Le VPN service, and (ii) the amount data transmitted (up- and download) during your session together with the IP address of the individual VPN server used by you. We do not store details of, or monitor, the websites you connect to when using our Le VPN Service. We only proceed with such storage so that we can monitor the performance of both our Site and Le VPN Service. For example it enables us to (i) sort server nodes by the number of users connected, (ii) limit your account to the number of connections which are included in your plan, (iii) carry out usage analysis for administrative purposes, and (iv) prevent abuse and fraud. This data is stored on our system for a certain period of time even though we have no obligation to store any such data.

**2\. Cookies**

Like many other websites, the Site may utilize a standard technology called a “cookie” to collect information about how the Site is used by users. Cookies were designed to help a website recognize previous visitors and thus save and remember any preferences such user may have set while browsing such a website. A cookie cannot retrieve any data from your hard drive, pass on a computer virus, or capture your e-mail address. We may utilize cookies within the Site in order to improve the Le VPN Service and your experience on the Site. Data collected via cookies allows us to statistically monitor how many people are using the Site. If you do not want information collected via cookies, there is a simple procedure utilized by most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature.

**3\. Data Protection & Security**

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone. Our Site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All data is protected using the most advanced methods available. We do not and will not actively monitor user sessions for inappropriate behaviour, nor do we maintain direct logs of any customer’s Internet activities. We do not store private information about any individual user’s activities on our network, such as emails, chats, VOIP calls, websites visited, etc.

**4\. Limited Disclosure & No Trading of your information**

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy. We will never sell your personal information to third parties.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

* if LE VPN is, or substantially all of its assets are, acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by LE VPN about its users will be one of the transferred assets, but will remain fully covered by this Privacy Policy; or

* if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of service and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or our safety, our users, or others; or

* if we receive a report from any person or organisation (including law enforcement) that leads us to suspect that your account has been used in connection with any wrong-doing, we may at our discretion suspend your account, but we will not disclose any personal information that may identify you unless we are legally compelled to do so.

**5\. Access to Your Personal Information**

You may also correct, update, or delete your personal information by making the change on your account page. We will retain your information for up to five years after your account has become inactive. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**6\. Links to Third Party Websites**

Our Site includes links to other websites the privacy practices of which may differ from those of LE VPN. If you submit personal information to any of those websites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.

**7\. Blog**

Our Site offers a publicly accessible blog that may require you to register to post a comment. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected and used by others who access them.We do have access to and are able control and moderate all information posted to the blog.

**8\. Social Media Widgets**

Our Site includes social media features, such as the Facebook, Twitter and Goole+ Like buttons and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our Site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the provisions of the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**9\. Copyright Violations**

If we receive complaints regarding copyrighted materials such as music and movies being shared over our network, we may filter traffic to see which account is sending it, and then we may cancel that account without a refund.

**II - Terms of Use**

**1\. Your status**

By registering to use our Le VPN Service you confirm that:

* you will provide accurate and complete registration data (including payment information) and that you shall inform us of any changes in your registration data;
* you are legally capable of entering into the present binding Terms of Use;
* if you are acting for an organisation (such as a company or a partnership), you are authorised to enter into the present Terms of Use for and on behalf of that organisation (in which case, references in these Terms of Use to "you" are to that organisation, and not you personally); and
* by accessing and using our Site and the Le VPN Service provided on our Site, you are complying with all applicable laws and regulations in the country in which you are located.

We reserve the right to refuse any subscription application for any reason or for no reason. We restrict access to our Le VPN Service to users who have registered with us and who have an active subscription. When you select the option to use our Le VPN Service, you will need to select a subscription plan and pay subscription fees in accordance with the provisions of these Terms of Use.

For security reasons, we may from time to time ask you for an electronic copy of your ID documents (Passport, National ID, driver’s license, etc.) (i) to verify your identify before your account’s activation, or (ii) if we suspect any misuse of your account or payment fraud. We do not store these documents on our servers and they are immediately deleted once the verification has been performed. When registering, Clients shall not use any methods to bypass our security filters or risk estimation mechanisms.

We may suspend or close the account you have with us and block your use of our Le VPN Service and Site, if (in our opinion) you have failed to comply with any provision of these Terms of Use.

You are responsible for ensuring that all persons who use your account with us are aware of these Terms of Use, and that they comply with them. You are responsible for all use of your security details and your account. You must treat your username and password, and any other security details, as confidential, and not disclose them to any other person. You must also prevent unauthorised access to your account.

**2\. Subscription Plans** **& Payment Terms**

Our Le VPN Service is available on subscription plans of various durations.

You may download our Software to an unlimited number of devices; however, each subscription only entitles you to the number of simultaneous connections as allowed by us in your subscription.

Your subscription is for your own personal use only and you may not rent, lend, hire out or otherwise share your connection with another person.

The plans we offer, and the prices, are as shown on our Site. You can select the subscription plan that best suits your needs. We can change our prices at any time, but changes will not affect any subscription that you have already paid for.

All fees are charged and payable in full in advance unless we agree otherwise.

You must pay us in one of the currencies stated on our Site. Payment can be made by debit or credit cards, by Bitcoin or through one of the payment methods, shown on our Site. If you setup a recurring payment, you authorise us to take payment in this way on an ongoing basis using the payment details you provide until you tell us to change your method of payment. If you wish to change your method or payment, or change your payment details, please tell us as soon as you can so that we can try to implement the change before subscription expires. If we are unable to take a recurring payment, your subscription will not be renewed.

If you purchase a subscription to our Le VPN Service via one of our authorised resellers, your agreement is with the reseller you have used, but you shall expressly accept our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy which will thus apply to you as if you were our direct customer as we are the supplier of the Le VPN Service.

We do not provide our Le VPN Service to clients residing in Hong Kong and do not accept payments from Hong Kong credit cards, Hong Kong Paypal accounts or any other means of payment coming from Hong Kong.

**3\. Refunds**

Clients are eligible for refund only for 30 days as of the date of first activation (which excludes any refund in case of renewals or new accounts if the user has already tried our Le VPN Service) of the Le VPN Service. Indeed, we offer a 30-day money back guarantee for new subscriptions, except for subscriptions purchased by mobile payment methods (for instance through App Store or iTunes) or by other alternative payment methods (for instance Qiwi, CashU, Openbucks, and other cash-based and alternative payment methods) which cannot be refunded (Refunds of iOS or iTunes in-app purchases (if user subscribes to the Le VPN Service from our app) should be processed directly with App Store or iTunes). If we cancel or suspend your account with us due to a breach by you of these Terms of Use or our Privacy Policy we will not refund any fees to you.

All refund requests are processed by our support team during the standard working hours from Monday to Friday, and the delay of the refund processing depends on the payment method used by each user and does not depend on LE VPN. Any refund request initiated through PayPal or any other payment dispute/claim system will lead to immediate account termination without a refund.

We will usually process the refund due to you as soon as possible and, in any case, within 30 days of the day we confirmed to you via e-mail that you were entitled to a refund. We will usually refund any money received from you using the same method originally used by you to pay for your subscription.

**4\. Prohibited Uses**

You may use our Site, Le VPN Service and Software only for personal and lawful purposes.

You may not use our Site, Le VPN Service and/or Software:

* to perform any security assessments including but not limited to penetration testing, security audits, ports scanning, vulnerability scanning, stress tests or DDoS (distributed denial-of-service);
* to resell, lease, distribute or provide our Le VPN Service to any third person;
* in any way that breaches any applicable local, national or international law or regulation;
* for the purpose of harming or attempting to harm minors in any way;
* in any way which contravenes the virus and hacking provisions as set out in Clause (Viruses, hacking and other offences);
* to upload, post, email or otherwise transmit any content that is directed to inciting or producing imminent conduct that is unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, tortuous, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, libellous, invasive of another's privacy, hateful, or racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable and is likely to produce such conduct;
* to send or transmit any illegal content, whether via e-mail, Usenet, or any other communication channel including but not limited to child pornography content;
* to impersonate any person or entity or otherwise misrepresent your affiliation with a person or entity;
* to attempt to access, probe, or connect to computing devices without proper authorization;
* to engage in any conduct that restricts or inhibits any other account holder from using or enjoying the Le VPN Service;
* for professional and/or business purposes namely with a view to hide the location from which the user actually operates any online business including web hosting services;
* to establish on one given device an encrypted VPN connection (as part of our Le VPN Service) inside another encrypted VPN connection (as part of our Le VPN Service or not);
* to establish more than one encrypted VPN connection on the same device;
* to forge headers or otherwise manipulate identifiers in order to disguise the origin of any content transmitted through the system;
* to upload, download, post, reproduce, distribute, email or otherwise transmit any content (i) protected by copyright without first having obtained permission of the copyright owner, or (ii) that infringes any patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright or other proprietary rights of any party;
* to upload, post, send, email or otherwise transmit any unsolicited or unauthorized advertising, promotional materials, "junk mail," "spam," "chain letters," or "pyramid schemes" via any communication channel;
* to interfere with or disrupt our Site's system or servers or networks connected to our Site's system, or disobey any requirements, procedures, policies or regulations of networks connected to our Site's system;
* to abuse our network so that it leads to degrade the Le VPN Service for other users;
* to collect or store personal data about other users without their knowledge; or
* to promote or provide instructional information about illegal activities, promote physical harm or injury against any group or individual, or promote any act of cruelty to animals.

You may only conduct P2P and file-sharing activities through the servers we specifically designated and dedicated for such activities.

**5\. Grant of licence**

In the event that we give you access to or allow you to download the Software, we will be granting you a non-exclusive, non-transferable licence to use the Software in accordance with its terms of use.

**6\. Intellectual property rights**

We are the owner or the licensee of all intellectual property rights in our Le VPN Service and nothing in these Terms of Use shall grant you any rights, title or interest in and to such intellectual property rights. All such intellectual property rights are reserved.

You must not use any part of the materials on our Site or the Software for commercial purposes without obtaining a licence to do so from us or from our licensors.

If you copy or download any part of our Site or of the Software in breach of these Terms of Use, your right to use our Site, our Le VPN Service and the Software will cease immediately and you must, at our option, remove any copies of the Software from your computer.

**7\. Viruses, hacking and other offences**

You must not misuse the Site, the Software or the Le VPN Service by knowingly introducing viruses, trojans, worms, logic bombs or other material which are malicious or technologically harmful. You must not attempt to gain unauthorised access to, interfere with, damage or disrupt, our Site, our Le VPN Service, the servers, equipment or network on which our Site or Le VPN Service is hosted, the Software used in the provision of our Site or Le VPN Service or any server, computer or database connected to our Site or Le VPN Service. You must not attack our Site or Le VPN Service via a denial-of-service attack or a distributed denial-of service attack. We will report any such criminal offences to the relevant law enforcement authorities and we will co-operate with those authorities by disclosing your identity to them. In the event of any such criminal breach, your right to use our Site or Le VPN Service will cease immediately.

We will not be liable for any loss or damage caused by a distributed denial-of-service attack, viruses or other technologically harmful material that may infect your computer equipment, computer programs, data or other proprietary material due to your use of our Site or Le VPN Service or due to your downloading of the Software, or on any website linked to it.

You must not reproduce, duplicate, copy or re-sell any part of our Site, our Le VPN Service or our Software in contravention of the provisions of these Terms of Use.

**8\. Affiliate Program**

We offer an affiliate program under which users can become affiliates of LE VPN. Such affiliate program is governed by the Rules & Requirements of the Affiliates Program with which participants must comply. The Rules & Requirements of the Affiliates Program is available at: https://www.le-vpn.com/affiliate-program/

**9\. Possible Measures in case of Material Breach**

Failure for you to comply with these Terms of Use constitutes a material breach (including but not limited to cases where a user provides fraudulent information upon subscription or is detected to represent a high-risk threat for the users of our network, etc.) of the Terms of Use and may result in our taking all or any of the following measures at our sole discretion and without notice:

* immediate, temporary or permanent withdrawal of your right to use our Site, Le VPN Service and/or Software with no refund (by either suspending or terminating your account with us); or
* issue of a warning to you; or
* removing, blocking, filtering or restricting by any means any activity, materials or information (including but not limited to e-mails) that we consider to constitute (i) an actual or potential violation of the Terms of Use (ii) a risk of liability for LE VPN or for its others customers ; or
* investigating the matter we consider to be illegal or to constitute a material breach of these Terms of Use; or
* legal proceedings against you for reimbursement of all costs on an indemnity basis (including, but not limited to, reasonable administrative and legal costs) resulting from the breach; or
* further legal action against you; or
* disclosure of such information to law enforcement authorities as we reasonably feel is necessary.
* blacklisting of the breaching user.

The responses described under this present section of the Terms of Use are not limited, and we may take any other action we reasonably deem appropriate.

**10\. Disclaimer of Warranties**

Our Le VPN Service and the Software are provided to you on an "as is" basis without any guarantees, conditions or warranties as to its quality or suitability for any particular purpose. We hereby expressly exclude all conditions, warranties and other terms which might otherwise be implied by statute, common law or the law of equity and make no representation or warranty, express or implied, as to the accuracy or completeness or satisfactory quality or fitness for a particular purpose of our Le VPN Service and/or the Software.

**11\. Duties and Liability**

11.1 User’s responsibilities

You shall be responsible and hold LE VPN harmless for:

* any action you take while using the Site, the Le VPN Service and the Software;
* any DMCA complaints filed by any third party against LE VPN on the basis of your actions;

You shall keep your devices healthy, well configured and not infected.

You shall respect our staff members by refraining from threatening or being verbally abusive with any of them.

11.2 Exclusion of Liability

To the extent permitted by law, LE VPN shall not be liable for any direct, indirect or consequential loss or damage incurred by you or any user in connection with our Le VPN Service and/or the Software, or in connection with the use, inability to use, or results of the use of our Le VPN Service, including, without limitation any liability for any:

* loss of income or revenue;
* loss of business;
* loss of profits or contracts;
* loss of anticipated savings;
* loss of, or damage caused to any client’s data or tangible property;
* loss of goodwill;
* failure to transmit client’s data into your computing device as part of the Le VPN Service;
* wasted management or office time; and
* other loss or damage of any kind, however arising and whether caused by tort (including negligence), breach of contract or otherwise, even if reasonably foreseeable.

**12\. Links from our site**

Where our Site or Software contains links to other websites and resources provided by third parties, these links are provided for your information only. We have no control over the contents of those sites or resources, and accept no responsibility or liability for them or for any loss or damage that may arise from your use of them.

**13\. Jurisdiction & Governing Law**

Considering that VTNV Solutions Limited is a limited company registered in Hong Kong with its registered office located at Unit 1109, 11/F., Kowloon Centre, 33 Ashley Road, Tsimshatsui, Kowloon, Hong Kong these Privacy Policy and Terms of Use shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region of the People's Republic of China.

The courts of the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region of the People's Republic of China will have jurisdiction over any claim arising from, or related to, a visit to our Site or use of our Le VPN Service or Software.

**14\. Entire agreement**

These Privacy Policy and Terms of Use constitute the entire agreement between you and us and supersede all previous discussions, correspondence, negotiations, previous arrangement, understanding or agreement between you and us relating to the subject matter hereof.

Last updated: September 2021

* 1311 Users Found This Useful

  Was this answer helpful? Yes No

###   Categories

[30

Alternative installation methods](https://le-vpn.com/clients/index.php/knowledgebase/164/Alternative-installation-methods)[20

Frequently Asked Questions](https://le-vpn.com/clients/index.php/knowledgebase/1/Frequently-Asked-Questions)[8

Le VPN Installation on mobile devices](https://le-vpn.com/clients/index.php/knowledgebase/21/Le-VPN-Installation-on-mobile-devices)[2

OpenVPN upgrade](https://le-vpn.com/clients/index.php/knowledgebase/304/OpenVPN-upgrade)[23

SmartDNS](https://le-vpn.com/clients/index.php/knowledgebase/135/SmartDNS)[4

Wireguard](https://le-vpn.com/clients/index.php/knowledgebase/294/Wireguard)

###   Categories

Alternative installation methods (30) Frequently Asked Questions (20) Le VPN Installation on mobile devices (8) OpenVPN upgrade (2) SmartDNS (23) Wireguard (4)

###   Tag Cloud

###   Support

© 2024 Le VPN. All Rights Reserved.

× Close

#### Title

Loading...

Loading...

Close Submit

× Close

#### English

×

#### Generate Password

Please enter a number between 8 and 64 for the password length

Password Length

Generated Password

Generate new password 

Close Copy to clipboard & Insert
